const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Which of these are forms of Weight Training?',
        answers: [
            'Weightlifting',
            'Powerlifting',
            'Strongman',
            'Bodybuilding',
            'All of the above',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'They are all types of weight training!',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Which form of weight training is best for gaining mass?',
        answers: [
            'Weightlifting',
            'Powerlifting',
            'Strongman',
            'Bodybuilding',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Bodybuilders are the mass monsters of the weight lifting world and the goal is to ultimately be be as big and aesthetically muscular as possible.',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Which style of weight training do olympic athletes use?',
        answers: [
            'Weightlifting',
            'Powerlifting',
            'Strongman',
            'Bodybuilding',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Weightlifting is where you\'ll see olympic athletes performing movements such as the clean and jerk, snatch and others',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Though various workouts are shared in the different styles of weight training, which single workout a staple in EVERY form of weight training?',
        answers: [
            'Bench press',
            'Squats',
            'Barbell curls',
            'Clean and jerk',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'No matter which style of weight lifting you choose the squat will always be one of the main workouts to used',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
      {
        question: 'Though various workouts are shared in the different styles of weight training, which single workout a staple in EVERY form of weight training?',
        answers: [
            'Bench press',
            'Squats',
            'Barbell curls',
            'Clean and jerk',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'No matter which style of weight lifting you choose the squat will always be one of the main workouts to used',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'In powerlifting, what is a “Total”',
        answers: [
            'How much you weigh',
            'How big your muscles are',
            'The sum of the 3 main lifts one rep maxes',
            'The sum of points earned in competition',
            'All of the above',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Powerlifters total is the sum of their best single rep of the 3 main lifts: squat, benchpress and deadlift',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Which forms of weight training is it OK to be “fat” even though weight training is used for general fitness?',
        answers: [
            'Weightlifting',
            'Powerlifting',
            'Strongman',
            'Bodybuilding',
            'All of the above',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'the heavier a person weighs, the more weight they can handle and powerlifters as well as strongmen end goal is ultimately lift the heaviest amount of weight possible',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the world record weight for the deadlift',
        answers: [
            '1301.6 lbs',
            '503.3 lbs',
            '1005 lbs',
            '1102.31 lbs',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The world record deadlift was set by strongman Eddie Hall lifting a whopping 1102.31 lbs, or 500kgs. The lift nearly killed the man!',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'Which form of weight training does performance enhancing drugs (steroids) run rampant in?',
        answers: [
            'Weightlifting',
            'Powerlifting',
            'Strongman',
            'Bodybuilding',
            'All of the above',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'In every form of weight training to be at the highest level atheletes use whatever means necessary to be as big and strong as possible',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'How much higher is the chance of dying as a professional bodybuilder?',
        answers: [
            '34%',
            '100%',
            '50%',
            'Not Applicable',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Bodybuilders end up using so many different drugs to be as big as muscular as possible but this is accompanied with many health issues',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    {
        question: 'There is only 4 forms of weight training.',
        answers: [
            'True',
            'False',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Weight training comes in other shapes and sizes such as crossfit and calisthenics',
        icon: '',
        alt: ''
    },
    
    

]